openhire.com 2006-06-21

# 

## Privacy Statement

Openhire.com is a wholly owned subsidiary of SilkRoad technology, inc. All policies of SilkRoad technology apply. OpenHire Inc. respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy outlines the information OpenHire Inc. may collect and how we may use that information.

### OpenHire Inc.'s Data Privacy Policy

OpenHire Inc. values your right to privacy and takes care to keep your personal identifying and security information safe, secure and confidential. Because of this we want to provide you with explicit information on how we collect, gather, and identify information during your experience using Openhire. This information may be expanded or updated as we change or develop our business services. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time-to-time to see if anything has changed. Your continued use of an OpenHire Inc. Business Service signifies your acceptance of our privacy policy.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email or postal address. OpenHire Inc. provides the Openhire Business Service to corporate Customers. Openhire is a recruiting management software tool. To satisfy a Customer's desire to use these technologies, OpenHire Inc. requires personal information about the individuals submitting resume data to the Openhire application.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected for the purpose of using the Openhire Inc. Business Service. OpenHire Inc. obtains personal information such as would appear on a resume from individual employment candidates. To facilitate the recruiting process, OpenHire Inc. provides the candidate's personal information to specific personnel at the OpenHire Inc. customer company that are responsible for the recruiting process. The data is used in the assessment and tracking of candidates, job openings, and reporting of recruiting data by the OpenHire Inc. customer. The collection of employment candidate data does not constitute a guarantee of an interview, job offer, hire or any contact by the OpenHire Inc. customer.

### Logged Files and Cookies

OpenHire Inc. Business Services may log IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes. These logs are analyzed to improve the Business Services and may serve as the basis for security investigations. These logs do not contain personal identifiable information.

OpenHire Inc. provides a permanent cookie that is not used to collect personally identifiable information. OpenHire Inc. uses cookies to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to the site and facilitate use of the site. This site also uses session cookies that track server-side data. These cookies are terminated once the user closes their browser but are required to use OpenHire Inc. Business Services.

### Links to Other Websites

Our web site contains links to information on other web sites. We do not have any control over these other web sites, and therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting those sites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, consult that site's privacy statement.

### How We Use Information

OpenHire Inc. uses this collected personal information for the purpose of facilitating our customer's requirements to track, assess, and report on candidate data.

The information OpenHire Inc. collects is used to perform the various business transactions to which our customers have subscribed, for internal review for the purpose of improving OpenHire Inc. Business Services, and to fulfill communication requests to designated company representatives.

OpenHire Inc. does not resell or share with other companies or entities any personal identifying, information gained through this process. OpenHire Inc. does characterize data in aggregate form for business performance management.

Please be advised that in certain circumstances, it may be necessary for OpenHire Inc. to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by our legal obligations.

### How To Opt-Out

As the personal information collected is for the purpose of facilitating a business transaction on behalf of an OpenHire Inc. customer, you have the ability to 'opt-out' by refraining from submitting your resume on the OpenHire Inc. customer's website.

### How to Access Your Information

Individuals can make changes to personal information and preferences by contacting the recruiting department of the OpenHire Inc. customer. In some cases, a customer may provide a means of updating resume information online. Personal information is required to use OpenHire Inc. Business Services.

Individuals can make inquiries or complaints about the use of their personal information, by contacting the customer company's recruiting department.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in addition to work with independent third parties, to safeguard and secure the information under our control.

### Your Consent

By using the Openhire Business Service to submit your resumes and associated data to an OpenHire Inc. customer, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy in addition to the information captured in your profile.

### Safe Harbor Enforcement

OpenHire Inc. is certified as compliant with the U.S. Department of Commerce under the "Safe Harbor Agreement" with the European Union. OpenHire Inc.agrees to investigate and resolve individual complaints or disputes, and have procedures in place for resolution.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:[openhire_support@silkroadtech.com](mailto:openhire_support@silkroadtech.com).
